

### CONTACT

- © 15 SWANAGE ROAD, BIRMINGHAM, SMALL HEATH B10 9ER
- 7404690414
- sazalbapary251194@gmail.com
- BANGLADESH
- AM/B/BE/f/k/q

#### SKILLS

- Precision assembly
- Packing and shipping procedures
- Basic equipment repairs
- Hand and power tools
- Quality control standards
- Expert assembler
- Manufacturing experience
- Safety procedure compliance

## LANGUAGES

English:

Beginner (A1)

Italian:

Proficient (C2)

Bengali:

Upper intermediate (B2)

# SAZAL BAPARY

### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Quick learner confident working in fast-paced production environments. Possesses solid skills in attention to detail, manual dexterity and observational skills. Adheres to strict procedures and takes action to manage safety risks. Motivated employee learns quickly in fast-paced, high-volume environments. Consistently adheres to safety standards. Maintains open availability and flexibility to work various shifts. Experienced Assembler knowledgeable about general warehouse operations. Works quickly and stays focused under strict deadlines. Skilled in managing multiple tasks with frequently changing priorities. Continuously projects positive attitude and seeks opportunities to help team members. Dependable self-starter experienced in manufacturing production, assembly, quality assurance and machine operation and maintenance.

### WORK HISTORY

Assembly worker

05/2022 - 10/2023

FANTIC MOTOR S.P.A - Santa Maria di Sala, ITALY

- Packed completed units, using safe packing techniques to avoid breakage.
- Maintained customer satisfaction by inspecting completed units, ensuring conformance with specifications and tolerances.
- Assembled 10+ components per hour, exceeding production target by 100%
- Contributed to implementation of safety training programmes, reducing accidents by 90%.
- Recommended actions to streamline assembly processes, reducing cycle times by 50%.
- Maximised equipment performance by completing planned preventative maintenance, including regular cleaning and testing.
- Assembled appliances, electrical equipment and metal products to required specifications.
- Aligned materials and merged parts to construct complex units.
- Collaborated with line group to assemble complicated products.
- · Measured parts to precisely fit components.
- · Utilised hand and power tools to fasttrack assembling process.
- Maintained clean and organised work areas for maximum productivity.
- Assembled component parts of FANTIC MOTOR products with attention to detail and focus on quality.
- Maintained equipment in good condition to avoid wear and tear.

Door supervisor

07/2021 - 05/2022

CDS S.R.L - Venice, ITALY

 Created and maintained secure, safe and welcoming environment for patrons.





- Maximised site security, maintaining effective communication with other door supervisors to coordinate conflict resolution actions.
- Guaranteed security of all entry and exit points with frequent foot patrols.
- Eliminated unauthorised access, performing thorough identification checks to grant entrance.
- · Checked ID cards and documented details in security log.

## **EDUCATION**

A-Levels: MECHANICS, 09/2009 - 07/2014 I.T.I.S FRANCESCO GIORDANI - Caserta, ITALY